Yury Misiyevich

Stack: JS, React, Redux (+hooks), CSS(+Grid,

Flexbox), HTML(+Pixel perfect), NodeJS, Git, jQuery,

Python + Flask, SQL (phpLiteAdmin), C.

Contacts mob: +375 29 167 02 62

e-mail: misiyevich@gmail.com

LinkedIn: Yury Misiyevich

Date of birth 05.05.1994

Objective

I'm looking for a front-end developer position to start my career. I have completed several courses recently include 0.5-year front-end course by The Rolling Scopes (EPAM) and now am ready to apply my skills and grow up as developer.

Projects

news app (Redux, React, JS)

interactive lumber calculator (React, JS)

web-animation creator (JS, Canvas)

DOM chat (JS, HTML, CSS)

■ <u>web-calendar with notes</u> (React)

dev.by parser (Node JS)

landing pages with Perfect Pixel (HTML, CSS)

validation adaptive form (JS, HTML, CSS)

songs-manager (React, JS)

validation adaptive form (JS, HTML, CSS)

task-manager (React, Redux)

hamburger adaptive menu (JS, HTML, CSS)

 sort algorithms, image recovery, database (structure "trie") etc. (C native)

shares-trading website (exchange) (Python + Flask, SQL (phpLiteAdmin))

Experience

2016 – present time

Repair and Maintenance Engineer at Heat and Power Plant

Key responsibilities:

 Leading of repair and construction site for the ventilation and aircondition systems

Team management

2013 - 2015, 2017 - 2018

Civil Engineer at Eurokan LLC

Key responsibilities:

 Settling , checking of acts of performed works and commissioning acts

Maintenance of executive documentation (BY, RU)

Education Languages

2011 - 2016	Heating, air conditioning, gas supply and air protection Belarusian National Technical University (Power plant construction and engineering services) (Av. score = 8.3)	Russian – Native English –Intermediate
2017 - 2018	Course CS50	
	Harvard (www.harvard.edu)	
2019	Front-end course	
	The Rolling Scopes (EPAM)	
2019	Siebel foundation	
	Service Desk	